Let's now go ahead and test to make sure that we can't enter the raffle whenever this raffle is not open or it's calculating.
让我们来测试一下，确保我们在未开放或是计算状态下确实是无法进入抽奖的
So we'll say it doesn't allow entrance, when raffle is Cal cumulating.
所以我们写 `it("doesnt allow entrance when raffle is calculating")`
And this will be an async function.
这里还是 `async function`
And first we'll enter will say await raffle dot enter raffle value is raffle entrance fee.
首先我们要写 `await raffle.enterRaffle()`
Now what we want to do we want to get this raffle into a closed state.
现在我们要让抽奖进入到关闭状态
So we want to get it out of its open state.
也就是我们想让它脱离开放状态
Well, how do we move this raffle from raffle dot open to raffle dot closed
那么我们该如何才能把抽奖从 "Raffle.OPEN" 转移到 "Raffle.CLOSE" 呢
in perform upkeep, remove the raffle from raffle that open to raffle dot calculating
在 "performUpkeep" 中，我们把抽奖从 "Raffle.OPEN" 转移到了 "Raffle.CALCULATING" 上
but perform upkeep can only be called if check upkeep returns true.
但 "performUpkeep" 只有在 "checkUpkeep" 返回 true 时才会被调用
Otherwise, it'll revert with raffle upkeep not needed.
否则它就会使用 "Raffle__UpkeepNotNeeded" 进行回滚
So what we need to do is we need to make check upkeep return true.
所以我们需要做的就是让 "checkUpkeep" 返回 true
And we will pretend to be the channeling keeper network
接着我们假装是 "Chainlink Keeper" 网络
to keep calling checkup keep waiting for it to be true.
去对 "checkUpkeep" 保持调用并等待它返回 true
And once we make it true, then we'll pretend to be the channeling keepers and call perform upkeep
一旦我们获得了 true，我们就假装成 "Chainlink Keepers" 去调用 "performUpkeep"
to put this contract in a state of calculating.
并把合约的状态改为 "CALCULATING"
Now how do we actually do that?
那我们该怎么做呢？
Well, in order for checkup keep to be true, we first need to see that we are indeed open,
嗯，为了让 "checkUpkeep" 为 true，首先就需要确保我们处于开放状态
which we are.
我们也的确是的
The next thing that we need to do though, is we need to do this time passed bit.
下一个需要做的是满足 "timePassed" 的要求
We need to actually wait that 30 seconds for time to pass.
我们需要等待 30 秒以通过这个时间
Now, that kind of sounds awful.
但这听起来有点扯啊
Do we have to wait 30 seconds for all of our tests?
难道我们必须要在所有测试中都等待 30 秒么？
What if our interval was 10 days
如果我们的 "interval" 是 10 天呢？
when we have to wait 10 days to run our tests?
我们就真在运行测试的时候等 10 天？
It sounds ridiculous.
这就有点搞笑了
Well, hard hat actually comes built in with a ton of functions for us to manipulate our blockchain to do literally whatever we want it to do.
实际上 hardhat 内置了大量的函数，让我们可以控制区块链以达到我们想要的目的
In the hard hat documentation.
在 hardhat 的文档中，
There's a section called Hard Hat Network reference inside the Hard Hat Network section.
有一个名为 "Hardhat Network Reference" 的部分，它在 "Hardhat Network" 部分里
And in here, there's a ton of information about how the hard hat network actually works and different configs that we can do with it.
这里有大量有关 Hardhat 网络如何运作以及我们能做哪些配置的信息
If we scroll down low enough, we can see the JSON RPC methods that we can use on this blockchain,
如果我们往下拉，就可以看到我们在链上用到的 "JSON-RPC methods"
we can do eath accounts block number call chinetti. We can do all these RPC methods that a normal blockchain has.
我们可以使用 "eth_accounts, blockNumber, call, chainId" 等所有一般区块链都具有的 "RPC" 方法
Additionally, we can do even more than that,
不止于此，我们还能做到更多的事情
we can use these things called Hard Hat Network methods.
我们还能使用这种被称为 "Hardhat network methods" 的方法
Since this is our local Hard Hat Network.
由于我们用的是本地的 Hardhat 网络
And we're using this for testing, we want to be able to test any scenario.
我们用它来进行测试，并且希望它可以在任何场景中进行测试
And it's these methods that give us the ability to do that,
而正是这些方法赋予了我们这样的能力
you can go through this and play around and see all the different things you can do.
你可以浏览一下这里，看一看都可以用到哪些不同的方法
One of them in particular is going to be set storage set
其中一个比较特殊的是这个 "setStorageAt"
where you can set storage at any place, which is really fun.
通过它你可以把 "storage" 设置在任何地方，是一个很有趣的功能
But some of the special testing debugging
methods are going to be EVM increase time, and EVM. Mine
increased time allows us to automatically increase the time
of our blockchain and EVM. Mine allows us to mine or create new
blocks, because if we increase the time, it doesn't do anything
unless there's a new block mined. So what we can do is we
can run a wait network, and we'll import network from Hard
Hat Network await network dot provider that send EVM in crease
time, comma, we can send a list of parameters to send with it,
which for us are just going to be our interval.to number. And
then we'll do plus one. Now right now, our interval isn't
stored globally, so we're probably going to want to do
that. So let's go ahead and do interval. And then in our before
each, we'll do interval equals await, raffle dot raffle dot get
interval, I'm just going to copy this and we're going to delete
this whole line. Wait raffle dot get interval. Since now we're
just going to call it interval at a global level, since we're
going to use it a lot. Now we're gonna say interval that to
number plus one. So we want to increase the time by whatever
our interval is to make sure that we can actually get that
checkup keep to return true. So additionally, we're going to
want to do a weight network dot provider. Dot send EVM mine with
an empty array just because we just want to mine it one extra
block. You can also do network dot provider that request with
an await here, these two would be basically the same, but this
one's a little quicker, right? So we've increased the time of
our blockchain. We've mined a block to move forward. It should
be open time has passed. Do we have a player? We do indeed,
because we've entered the raffle. We should have a balance
because we've entered the right Apple, check upkeep should now
return true. So we should be able to call perform upkeep and
pretend to be a chain lock keeper. So we're going to
pretend to be a chain the keeper and call await raffle dot
perform upkeep. And we're going to pass this some empty call
data just by passing a blank array like that. And now this
should be in a calculating state. So now that it's in a
calculating state, we can say our enter raffle reverts
correctly if the raffle isn't open. So now we'll say await,
expect raffle dot enter, raffle. And we'll send it value of
raffle entrance fee. We're expecting this.to dot b dot
reverted with that raffle underscore underscore not open
error. Okay, let's try just this in our tests now. So we'll run
Hardhead test dash dash grep. Put this in quotes. And perfect
that passes as well.